Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 1986
    - No. 1326, 1986-12-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0596 (Box 60)
    - No. 1327, 1986-12-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0597 (Box 60)
    - No. 1328, 1986-12-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0597 (Box 60)
  - Videorecordings, 1987
    - No. 1329, 1987-01-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0597 (Box 60)
    - No. 1330, 1987-01-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0598 (Box 60)
    - No. 1331, 1987-01-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0598 (Box 60)
    - No. 1332, 1987-01-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0598 (Box 60)
    - No. 1333, 1987-01-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0599 (Box 60)
    - No. 1334, 1987-02-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0599 (Box 60)
    - No. 1335, 1987-02-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0599 (Box 60)
    - No. 1336, 1987-02-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0600 (Box 61)
    - No. 1337, 1987-02-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0600 (Box 61)
    - No. 1338, 1987-03-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0600 (Box 61)
    - No. 1338, 1987-03-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0601; duplicate (Box 61)
    - No. 1339, 1987-03-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0602 (Box 61)
    - No. 1340, 1987-03-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0602 (Box 61)
    - No. 1341, 1987-03-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0602 (Box 61)
    - No. 1342, 1987-04-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0603 (Box 61)
    - No. 1343, 1987-04-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0603 (Box 61)
    - No. 1344, 1987-04-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0603 (Box 61)
    - No. 1345, 1987-04-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0604 (Box 61)
    - No. 1346, 1987-05-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0604 (Box 61)
    - No. 1347, 1987-05-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0604 (Box 61)
    - No. 1348, 1987-05-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0605 (Box 61)
    - No. 1349, 1987-05-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0605 (Box 61)
    - No. 1350, 1987-05-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0605 (Box 61)
    - No. 1351, 1987-06-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0606 (Box 61)
    - No. 1352, 1987-06-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0606 (Box 61)
    - No. 1401, 1987-06-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0606 (Box 61)
    - No. 1402, 1987-06-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0607 (Box 62)
    - No. 1403, 1987-07-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0607 (Box 62)
    - No. 1404, 1987-07-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0607 (Box 62)
    - No. 1405, 1987-07-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0608 (Box 62)
    - No. 1406, 1987-07-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0608 (Box 62)
    - No. 1407, 1987-08-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0608 (Box 62)
    - No. 1408, 1987-08-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0609 (Box 62)
    - No. 1409, 1987-08-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0609 (Box 62)
    - No. 1410, 1987-08-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0609 (Box 62)
    - No. 1411, 1987-08-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0610 (Box 62)
    - No. 1412, 1987-09-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0610 (Box 62)
    - No. 1413, 1987-09-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0610 (Box 62)
    - No. 1414, 1987-09-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0611 (Box 62)
    - No. 1415, 1987-09-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0611 (Box 62)
    - No. 1416, 1987-10-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0611 (Box 62)
    - No. 1417, 1987-10-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0612 (Box 62)
    - No. 1418, 1987-10-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0612 (Box 62)
    - No. 1419, 1987-10-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0612 (Box 62)
    - No. 1420, 1987-10-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0613 (Box 62)
    - No. 1421, 1987-11-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0613 (Box 62)
    - No. 1422, 1987-11-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0613 (Box 62)
    - No. 1423, 1987-11-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0614 (Box 63)
    - No. 1424, 1987-11-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0614 (Box 63)
    - No. 1425, 1987-12-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0614 (Box 63)
    - No. 1426, 1987-12-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0615 (Box 63)
    - No. 1427, 1987-12-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0615 (Box 63)
    - No. 1428, 1987-12-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0615 (Box 63)
    - No. 1429, 1987-12-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0616 (Box 63)
  - Videorecordings, 1988
    - No. 1430, 1988-01-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0616 (Box 63)
    - No. 1431, 1988-01-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0616 (Box 63)
    - No. 1432, 1988-01-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0617 (Box 63)
    - No. 1433, 1988-01-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0617 (Box 63)
    - No. 1434, 1988-02-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0617 (Box 63)
    - No. 1435, 1988-02-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0618 (Box 63)
    - No. 1436, 1988-02-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0618 (Box 63)
    - No. 1437, 1988-02-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0618 (Box 63)
    - No. 1438, 1988-03-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0619 (Box 63)
    - No. 1439, 1988-03-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0619 (Box 63)
    - No. 1440, 1988-03-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0619 (Box 63)
    - No. 1441, 1988-03-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0620 (Box 63)
    - No. 1442, 1988-04-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0620 (Box 63)
    - No. 1443, 1988-04-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0620 (Box 63)
    - No. 1444, 1988-04-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0621 (Box 64)
    - No. 1445, 1988-04-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0621 (Box 64)
    - No. 1446, 1988-04-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0621 (Box 64)
    - No. 1447, 1988-05-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0622 (Box 64)
    - No. 1448, 1988-05-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0622 (Box 64)
    - No. 1449, 1988-05-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0622 (Box 64)
    - No. 1450, 1988-05-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0623 (Box 64)
    - No. 1451, 1988-06-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0623 (Box 64)
    - No. 1452, 1988-06-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0623 (Box 64)
    - No. 1501, 1988-06-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0624 (Box 64)
    - No. 1502, 1988-06-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0624 (Box 64)
    - No. 1503, 1988-07-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0624 (Box 64)
    - Inside Albany: Critical Choices Convention, 1988-07-01; VHS; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0502 (Box 46)
    - No. 1504, 1988-07-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0625 (Box 64)
    - No. 1505, 1988-07-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0625 (Box 64)
    - No. 1506, 1988-07-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0625 (Box 64)
    - No. 1507, 1988-07-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0626 (Box 64)
    - No. 1508, 1988-08-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0626 (Box 64)
    - No. 1509, 1988-08-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0626 (Box 64)
    - No. 1510, 1988-08-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0627 (Box 64)
    - No. 1511, 1988-08-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0627 (Box 64)
    - No. 1512, 1988-09-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0627 (Box 64)
    - No. 1513, 1988-09-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0628 (Box 65)
    - No. 1514, 1988-09-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0628 (Box 65)
    - No. 1515, 1988-09-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0628 (Box 65)
    - No. 1516, 1988-10-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0629 (Box 65)
    - No. 1517, 1988-10-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0629 (Box 65)
    - No. 1518, 1988-10-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0629 (Box 65)
    - No. 1519, 1988-10-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0630 (Box 65)
    - No. 1520, 1988-10-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0630 (Box 65)
    - No. 1521, 1988-11-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0630 (Box 65)
    - No. 1522, 1988-11-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0631 (Box 65)
    - No. 1523, 1988-11-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0631 (Box 65)
    - No. 1524, 1988-11-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0631 (Box 65)
    - No. 1525, 1988-12-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0632 (Box 65)
    - No. 1526, 1988-12-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0632 (Box 65)
    - No. 1527, 1988-12-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0632 (Box 65)
    - No. 1528, 1988-12-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0633 (Box 65)
    - No. 1529, 1988-12-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0633 (Box 65)
  - Videorecordings, 1989
    - No. 1530, 1989-01-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0633 (Box 65)
    - No. 1531, 1989-01-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0634 (Box 65)
    - No. 1532, 1989-01-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0634 (Box 65)
    - No. 1533, 1989-01-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0634 (Box 65)
    - No. 1534, 1989-02-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0635 (Box 66)
    - No. 1535, 1989-02-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0635 (Box 66)
    - No. 1536, 1989-02-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0635 (Box 66)
    - No. 1537, 1989-02-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0636 (Box 66)
    - No. 1538, 1989-03-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0636 (Box 66)
    - No. 1539, 1989-03-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0636 (Box 66)
    - No. 1540, 1989-03-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0637 (Box 66)
    - No. 1541, 1989-03-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0637 (Box 66)
    - No. 1542, 1989-03-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0637 (Box 66)
    - No. 1543, 1989-04-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0638 (Box 66)
    - No. 1544, 1989-04-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0638 (Box 66)
    - No. 1545, 1989-04-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0638 (Box 66)
    - No. 1546, 1989-04-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0639 (Box 66)
    - No. 1547, 1989-05-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0639 (Box 66)
    - No. 1548, 1989-05-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0639 (Box 66)
    - No. 1549, 1989-05-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0640 (Box 66)
    - No. 1550, 1989-05-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0640 (Box 66)
    - No. 1551, 1989-06-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0640 (Box 66)
    - No. 1552, 1989-06-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0641 (Box 66)
    - No. 1601, 1989-06-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0641 (Box 66)
    - No. 1602, 1989-06-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0641 (Box 66)
    - No. 1603, 1989-06-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0642 (Box 67)
    - No. 1604, 1989-07-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0642 (Box 67)
    - No. 1605, 1989-07-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0642 (Box 67)
    - No. 1606, 1989-07-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0643 (Box 67)
    - No. 1607, 1989-07-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0643 (Box 67)
    - No. 1608, 1989-08-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0643 (Box 67)
    - No. 1609, 1989-08-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0644 (Box 67)
    - No. 1610, 1989-08-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0644 (Box 67)
    - No. 1611, 1989-08-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0644 (Box 67)
    - No. 1612, 1989-09-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0645 (Box 67)
    - No. 1613, 1989-09-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0645 (Box 67)
    - No. 1614, 1989-09-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0645 (Box 67)
    - No. 1615, 1989-09-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0646 (Box 67)
    - No. 1616, 1989-09-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0646 (Box 67)
    - No. 1617, 1989-10-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0646 (Box 67)
    - No. 1618, 1989-10-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0647 (Box 67)
    - No. 1619, 1989-10-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0647 (Box 67)
    - No. 1620, 1989-10-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0647 (Box 67)
    - No. 1621, 1989-11-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0648 (Box 67)
    - No. 1622, 1989-11-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0648 (Box 67)
    - No. 1623, 1989-11-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0648 (Box 67)
    - No. 1624, 1989-11-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0649 (Box 67)
    - No. 1625, 1989-12-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0649 (Box 67)
    - No. 1626, 1989-12-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0649 (Box 67)
    - No. 1627, 1989-12-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0650 (Box 68)
    - No. 1628, 1989-12-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0650 (Box 68)
    - No. 1629, 1989-12-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0650 (Box 68)
  - Videorecordings, 1990
    - No. 1630, 1990-01-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0651 (Box 68)
    - No. 1631, 1990-01-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0651 (Box 68)
    - No. 1632, 1990-01-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0651 (Box 68)
    - No. 1633, 1990-01-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0652 (Box 68)
    - No. 1634, 1990-02-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0652 (Box 68)
    - No. 1635, 1990-02-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0652 (Box 68)
    - No. 1636, 1990-02-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0653 (Box 68)
    - No. 1637, 1990-02-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0653 (Box 68)
    - No. 1638, 1990-03-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0653 (Box 68)
    - No. 1639, 1990-03-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0654 (Box 68)
    - No. 1640, 1990-03-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0654 (Box 68)
    - No. 1641, 1990-03-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0654 (Box 68)
    - No. 1642, 1990-03-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0655 (Box 68)
    - No. 1643, 1990-04-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0655 (Box 68)
    - No. 1644, 1990-04-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0655 (Box 68)
    - No. 1645, 1990-04-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0656 (Box 68)
    - No. 1646, 1990-04-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0656 (Box 68)
    - No. 1647, 1990-05-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0656 (Box 68)
    - No. 1648, 1990-05-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0657 (Box 68)
    - No. 1649, 1990-05-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0657 (Box 68)
    - No. 1650, 1990-05-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0657 (Box 68)
    - No. 1651, 1990-06-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0658 (Box 68)
    - No. 1652, 1990-06-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0658 (Box 68)
    - No. 1701, 1990-06-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0658 (Box 68)
    - No. 1702, 1990-06-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0659 (Box 69)
    - No. 1703, 1990-06-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0659 (Box 69)
    - No. 1704, 1990-07-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0659 (Box 69)
    - No. 1705, 1990-07-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0660 (Box 69)
    - No. 1706, 1990-07-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0660 (Box 69)
    - No. 1707, 1990-07-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0660 (Box 69)
    - No. 1708, 1990-08-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0661 (Box 69)
    - No. 1709, 1990-08-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0661 (Box 69)
    - No. 1710, 1990-08-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0661 (Box 69)
    - No. 1711, 1990-08-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0662 (Box 69)
    - No. 1712, 1990-08-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0662 (Box 69)
    - No. 1713, 1990-09-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0662 (Box 69)
    - No. 1714, 1990-09-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0663 (Box 69)
    - No. 1715, 1990-09-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0663 (Box 69)
    - No. 1716, 1990-09-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0663 (Box 69)
    - No. 1717, 1990-10-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0664 (Box 69)
    - No. 1718, 1990-10-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0664 (Box 69)
    - No. 1719, 1990-10-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0664 (Box 69)
    - No. 1720, 1990-10-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0665 (Box 69)
    - No. 1721, 1990-11-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0665 (Box 69)
    - No. 1722, 1990-11-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0665 (Box 69)
    - No. 1723, 1990-11-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0666 (Box 69)
    - No. 1724, 1990-11-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0666 (Box 69)
    - No. 1725, 1990-12-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0666 (Box 69)
    - No. 1726, 1990-12-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0667 (Box 70)
    - No. 1727, 1990-12-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0667 (Box 70)
    - No. 1728, 1990-12-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0667 (Box 70)
    - No. 1729, 1990-12-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0668 (Box 70)
  - Videorecordings, 1991
    - No. 1730, 1991-01-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0668 (Box 70)
    - No. 1731, 1991-01-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0668 (Box 70)
    - No. 1732, 1991-01-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0669 (Box 70)
    - No. 1733, 1991-01-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0669 (Box 70)
    - No. 1734, 1991-02-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0669 (Box 70)
    - No. 1735, 1991-02-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0670 (Box 70)
    - No. 1736, 1991-02-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0670 (Box 70)
    - No. 1737, 1991-02-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0671 (Box 70)
    - No. 1738, 1991-03-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0670 (Box 70)
    - No. 1739, 1991-03-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0672 (Box 70)